<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>MyRoom - I want that (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.MyRoomIWantThat</packageId>
  <author>AliceCecil</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/MyRoomIWantThat</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of AliceCecils mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1541796376

- Added setting for level of impressiveness wanted
- Added setting for minimum space wanted
- Pawns will not place larger items where they block the doorway
- Pawns will try to place items along the wall if possible
- Rotatable objects placed along a wall will face outwards
- Pawns will not add beds to their room (I will see if I can make them replace their bed instead)
- Pawns will not try to place multiple blueprints in one room at the same time

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/MyRoomIWantThat][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Pawns do stuff to their own rooms from available minified things.


Right now on rare tick pawn will look for a minified thing they find beautiful to make their room impressive up to their threshold. 
ie normal folks like an Impressive Room and will install art you got lying around to get there. 
and Greedy people will always. 
and Astetics will never.

pawns will rarely rearrange their rooms as well.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>